<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Yorokka]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Yorokka</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 08:25:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 08:25:49 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[Penelope Patches Powell]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>Penelope Patches Powell</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Campaign Catalyst Overview]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>The Old Gods [WIP]

<br>The Old Gods are enigmatic, not much is known about their metaphysical nature. They are perceived as being responsible for the universe and even older than it. In that respect they are quite alien, being born of something else that we made our gods.
<br>Their powers tend to be around their domains, however this is not known to be a rule for them, perhaps it is a categorisation bestowed to them. There is no reason for them to follow any human or universal rules.
<br>Though they are worshipped by humanity, humanity has rarely been spoken to by them. Perhaps they cannot speak our language and us theirs.

<br>Fifteen centuries past, when the world was still young and the Old Gods walked upon earthly soil while humanity followed in their shadow. Tribes grew into chiefdoms and swelled into dense states. The delicate foundations of peace crumbled under the weight of opposing beliefs. Blood flowed into rivers and stained the earth in ways the Gods had not yet seen, their alien hearts heavy with dismay and the threat of a war of their own. To mend humanity’s fracture, they sent forth an ambassador – Vitruvius, the Godchild; born from the skull of a Nyaxl peasant. He was a unity of divinity and mortality with a mission to unite humanity under a single banner and to weave order from chaos.<br>But the night had other plans.<br>A torrential downpour black blood rained from the heavens as a being, new to all, carved itself from the moon. A blossom of wings leaving behind an ivory carcass. Its song, a lullaby to the world, called forth the nightmares of both humanity and the divine to rise from its tarry blood. What followed was a war of unmatched proportions. The two God children fought, the Old Gods fought, humanity fought. Amidst the chaos, some humans found methods to attain divine might for themselves which only served to further the fighting.<br>Vitruvius, The Godchild [WIP]

<br>After Dal’mela was vanquished, he sought to continue his quest of uniting all of humanity under one banner. To do so he felt he needed help so he took the hand of Nyaxl’s queen in marriage and used her armies to accomplish this.
<br>Vitruvius upon bringing his conquest into Ashkov (an apostatic state) was captured. His limbs were broken as he was tied to a breaking wheel and set alight to mock the Gods. Ashkov worships the might of humanity itself.

<br>When the dust settled, the Old Gods vanished into myth. Dal’mela fell to Vitruvius, as Vitruvius himself was slain by mortal hands – the last vestiges of embodied divinity lingered in the hearts of the devout and the hearts of tiny human gods and Kydel, continent of Dal’mela’s landing, scorched of any life.<br>Left to their own devices, humanity stumbled forward, carrying the weight of their fractured legacy. Until five centuries ago.<br><br>
<br>
<br><br><br>Five centuries ago. Beneath the light of a moon bloated and pale, an army of the Verenaric marched upon the forest mountain keep of Alanera. The rumors of cultic worshippers brought them here, the whispers of esoteric tongues carried on the wind reinforced their purpose – to cull this bedlam before it spread.<br>Nearby townsfolk watched as the emboldened soldiery fared forth into the arboreal dark. Dawn came, then left. No soldiers returned – the townsfolk questioned what happened, dusk brought an answer. The thud footfalls, too heavy, too wrong.<br>What emerged was not human; but a congress of teeth and claws led by a Shepherd of chaos with a Wolf slunk in the shadow of his heel. The air tasted of rust and prophecy as the Shepherd proclaimed himself to be the first son of Dal’mela – and thus began the Age of Torment which humanity would face alone.<br>Soon, the rest of Dal’mela’s brood seeped from cracks in the world:<br>
<br>Aemalea, whose breath festered in the shadowed corners of plague-struck homes.
<br>The Vacuous, a mindless beast clawing at the unlit hearths of ruins.
<br>Madre’us, whose fingers curled like worms in the marrow of the dead.
<br>Lamellae, singing lullabies to the drowned of fathoms light will never reach.
<br>Monno, a wisp of hunger in the shaded sockets of children’s eyes.
<br>Humanity, once again, was left to its own devices.<br>Verenar was left a carcass of a kingdom but refused to kneel. As the new Queen was crowned, she found a way to ascend with methods still unknown, but she would not treat herself as a God. She would instead use her ascension to uncover a gift in which she would hand down to her people, a way to harness magic from their own blood. No worship, prayers or pacts required – just a knife, a will, and a price paid in a scarlet currency. The Sun had saved humanity this time but whatever came next humanity would save itself.<br>Now in the present, the shadows stir again. The tiny gods watch. And humanity, ever alone, tightens its grip on the blade for what’s to come.<br>The wheel turns. The blood remains and a Wolf smirks at the challenge.<br><br><br>
<br>Verenar
<br>Ashkov
<br>Nyaxl
<br>Korovia
<br>Norovok
<br>Kydel
<br>Hiya, by smashing a few bits of code hard enough together I made a simple tab-switching multi-image wiki-infobox ! For now I use it mostly for switching my dungeon layers on the quick box, i suppose I'll be able to track more things too with it hehe<br>Here's the code if someone wants to see ! (sorry for the format):<br>Infobox

F1 B1 
Tabbed box
<img alt="cover wsmall" src="\lib\media\ipos.png">
<img alt="cover wsmall" src="\lib\media\ipos.png">





<br>personally i would do it something like this i guess<br>Evaluation Error: SyntaxError: Unexpected token '&lt;'
    at DataviewInlineApi.eval (plugin:dataview:18638:21)
    at evalInContext (plugin:dataview:18639:7)
    at asyncEvalInContext (plugin:dataview:18646:16)
    at DataviewJSRenderer.render (plugin:dataview:18670:19)
    at DataviewJSRenderer.onload (plugin:dataview:18260:14)
    at e.load (app://obsidian.md/app.js:1:1166456)
    at DataviewApi.executeJs (plugin:dataview:19198:18)
    at DataviewPlugin.dataviewjs (plugin:dataview:20068:18)
    at eval (plugin:dataview:19967:124)
    at app://obsidian.md/app.js:1:1221851
    at t.postProcess (app://obsidian.md/app.js:1:1297472)
    at t.postProcess (app://obsidian.md/app.js:1:1296300)
    at renderMarkdownView (plugin:webpage-html-export:70601:21)
    at async Object.renderFile (plugin:webpage-html-export:70515:16)
    at async Object.renderFile (plugin:webpage-html-export:70399:18)
    at async Webpage.populateDocument (plugin:webpage-html-export:66412:22)
    at async Webpage.create (plugin:webpage-html-export:66342:30)
    at async Website.createWithFiles (plugin:webpage-html-export:68935:25)
    at async HTMLExporter.exportFiles (plugin:webpage-html-export:74683:19)
    at async HTMLExporter.export (plugin:webpage-html-export:74675:19)<br><br>Roll DV<br>Dataview: No results to show for list query.<br><br>worshipers: 5<br>
worshiper_ranges:<br>
<br>1 to 5
<br>6 to 10
<br>11 to 20
<br>21 to 40
<br>41 or more
<br><br>Influence from Worshipers: [MB_UNLOADED] input field [MB_UNLOADED] view field]]></description><link>publish\campaign-catalyst-overview.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Publish/Campaign Catalyst Overview.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Penelope Patches Powell]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:04:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\ipos.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\ipos.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Homebrew & Websites]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>]]></description><link>publish\homebrew-&amp;-websites.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Publish/Homebrew &amp; Websites.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Penelope Patches Powell]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 08:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[index]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Index Page]]></description><link>publish\index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Publish/index.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Penelope Patches Powell]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 08:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Morana]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Infobox

<img alt="z_Assets/Art Reference/Winter Spirit Morana 01.png" src="\lib\media\winter-spirit-morana-01.png">




<br><br><br>Letters
Dataview: No results to show for table query.
<br>Literature
Dataview: No results to show for table query.
<br>Rumours
Dataview: No results to show for table query.
<br><br>Details: Ancient, tall, winter fey of starvation <br>
Physical: Pristine pointed ivory antlers, cascading snow white hair, pallid skin, a third eye within the central forehead and a fluffy leopard-esk tail. <br>
Clothing:&nbsp;A heavy pelt covers most their form, it's slightly reddish entire giving the appearance they crawled inside of something to keep warm. <br><br>
<br>The Winter Spirit of Starvation and Death.
<br>Their current goals are to keep watch of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Ipos" data-href="Ipos" href="\campaign\parties\characters\party-1\ipos.html" class="internal-link data-link-icon data-link-icon-after data-link-text" target="_self" rel="noopener" data-link-tags="#To-Do #Character #Player" data-link-path="Campaign/Parties/Characters/Party 1/Ipos.md" style="--data-link-tags: #To-Do #Character #Player; --data-link-path: Campaign/Parties/Characters/Party 1/Ipos.md;">aberrant undead bear</a> hunting around the mountain. During these hunts Morana may seek to torment the hunting party, appearing to be a deer - or the distant promise of food - before disappearing the moment they get closer.
<br>You can hear their snickering laugh on the cold winter winds.
]]></description><link>publish\morana.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Publish/Morana.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Penelope Patches Powell]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 08:15:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\winter-spirit-morana-01.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\winter-spirit-morana-01.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>